<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Caifeng</title><link>https://baocaifeng.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Caifeng</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:39:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://baocaifeng.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Linux</title><link>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/basic/os/linux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:36:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/basic/os/linux/</guid><description>This post indicates the possible steps or problems that I have met when install Debian on my old computer. It&amp;rsquo;s not a beginning tutorial with too many details. If you have no experience of any other linux os installation, you better find other tutorials in case to wast more time. If you have already some experience of linux os installation like Ubunto, Mint, Kali, whatever, and you have also an old computer that you don&amp;rsquo;t want to throught it away, then this post may help you a little.</description></item><item><title>Big Data</title><link>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/interview/qa/big-data/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 13:28:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/interview/qa/big-data/</guid><description>H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 How do you prepare data? What is your approach to it?
Can you explain how Big Data is connected to Hadoop?
Can you define the terms HDFS and YARN for us? Also, tell us their respective components
What are the Edge Nodes in Hadoop?
What exactly is ‘indexing’ in HDFS?
What do you understand from commodity hardware?</description></item><item><title>Markdown Samples</title><link>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/markdown-sample/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/markdown-sample/</guid><description>This is a sample post intended to test the followings:
A different post author. Table of contents. Markdown content rendering. Math rendering. Emoji rendering. Markdown Syntax Rendering Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt; is the highest section level while &amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; is the lowest.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur?</description></item><item><title>Rich Content</title><link>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/category/sub-category/rich-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/category/sub-category/rich-content/</guid><description>This sample post tests the followings:
Category, sub-category nesting in the sidebar. Hero image and other images are in images folder inside this post directory. Different media rendering like image, tweet, YouTube video, Vimeo video etc. Image Sample Tweet Sample {{/&amp;lt; twitter 1085870671291310081 &amp;gt;/}}
YouTube Video Sample Vimeo Video Sample</description></item><item><title>Shortcodes Samples</title><link>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/shortcodes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://baocaifeng.github.io/posts/shortcodes/</guid><description>This is a sample post intended to test the followings:
Default hero image. Different shortcodes. Alert The following alerts are available in this theme.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;success&amp;quot;.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;danger&amp;quot;.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;warning&amp;quot;.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;info&amp;quot;.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;dark&amp;quot;.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;primary&amp;quot;.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;secondary&amp;quot;.</description></item></channel></rss>